so computer architecture is about
building future computers and let's see
how it interacts with technology trends
so progress in computer manufacturing
technology is very fast so if we design
with current technology and using the
parts they already have for a computer
by the time we designed a new computer
we have an obsolete new computer why
well because by the time we have
designed it with current technology in
parts the technology and the pieces for
computers have improved so what we have
is something that is using obsolete
technology and obsolete components so we
must anticipate future technology and
what will be available and then when we
design computer that way we get future
computers that actually use the most
advanced technology available at the
time but how do we do that we must be
aware of technology trends that is how
do we expect technology to change in the
future and what do we expect to be
available in the future